DOCUMENTATION

CUSTOMERS
The Email can be set to NULL because I didn't consider mandatory for the restaurant to record all customers' emails.
The Phone Number attribute is also a unique key, because it can identify a customer. The same doesn't apply for the email, because it can evaluate to NULL.

EMPLOYEES
The Phone Number and Email attributes are also unique keys, because they can identify an employee. I decided not to include in the unique keys set the Address attribute, because there could be the possibility that two employees share the same address.

BOOKINGS
Each customer can make several bookings. The Date and Time attrbitute take into account both the date and the time of arrival of the customer.

MENUS
Each menu belongs to a specific cuisine (Italian, Greek, French, and so on).

ITEMS
Each item belongs to a specific category (starters, courses, drinks and desserts). An item can belong to many menus, and a menu has many items in it. This is why I established a N:N relationship between these two tables.
As an example of an item belonging to different menus, we can consider a bottle of water. Using this schema, the bottle of water can be included in the drinks section of many different menus.
In addition, the item Name is a unique key, in order to avoid duplicated data.

ORDERS
Each booking has multiple orders. Also, each menu can be selected in several orders. Between the Orders table and the Employees table I established a N:N relationship because:
- an order can be executed by different employees (Head Chef, Assistant Chef, Head Waiter, Waiter, Cashier)
- an employee executes different orders.

ORDER DELIVERY STATUS
This weak entity considers the status of each order. The difference between Order Date and Time and Delivery Date and Time is the following:
- the Order Date and Time attributes considers when the order is requested
- the Delivery Date and Time attributes considers when the employee responsible delivered his/her task, subsequently updating the status.
As an example, this could be a possible series of events:
1. Order requested (creating orderID, OrderDate and OrderTime)
2. Employee begins working the order (OrderDeliveryStatus set to <Name of the Task> - InProgress)
3. Employee completes his/her task (OrderDeliveryStatus set to <Name of the Task> - Completed)
4. Order passes to another employee, repeating step 2 and 3 OR Order completed if this was the last employee (the Cashier, for example). 



